Ta-Taichi!
H-Hey...
You didn't need to rush here.
But...
You sent an e-mail saying
that you wanted to talk.
So, Nagase...
I did some thinking,
and I realized that I'm a selfish
and self-centered person.
Once my mind is made up,
I lock myself in and ignore all
other possible conclusions.
And if I think I'm
right about something,
I'll never admit that I'm wrong.
That's why I ended up hurting
Inaba, arguing with Aoki,
and hurt you, too.
I'm a selfish jerk.
So I thought I should keep my distance
to avoid hurting anyone.
But when I actually tried to
distance myself, I realized
that I want to be with you guys.
Instead of staying away to
avoid hurting everyone,
I'd rather stay together and risk it.
So, if you don't mind,
can I stay by your side?
That's not fair, Taichi.
Er, uh...
I've been working hard to
keep everyone together.
But everyone was getting hurt,
so I figured it was inevitable
that we'd fall apart.
I was convinced of that.
But now you say it doesn't matter
if we all hurt each other?
Well, it does make sense.
But I never thought I'd hear you say
that it doesn't matter if
we hurt each other.
Yeah, I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
Are you going to tell
everyone else what you
just told me and bring
back the whole club?
That's the plan.
This doesn't feel right.
I was trying hard, but then you
just took it all upon yourself.
Uh, well...
You're definitely a selfish jerk.
But your head is usually
in the right place.
Even if your methods aren't the best.
My sister said something similar.
That's why I ended up injuring you.
I thought you said it's inevitable
that we'd hurt each other?
I didn't mean physically.
It's okay. I forgive you.
Okay.
First, I'll talk to Inaban.
I'll call Aoki.
Okay, let's give it our best shot!
Yeah!
It's been a while.
Yeah.
So, Aoki...
I said some terrible things
to you the other day.
I was too arrogant and full of myself.
I was convinced that I could
do everything myself.
But that was wrong!
I can't undo the wrong I've done,
but I want to apologize!
Sorry!
Aoki?
Damn you!
You beat me to the punch!
Yeah, so...
I was also going to apologize.
Huh?
When you called me, I knew
you'd already beaten me to it.
It really hurt when Iori-chan
said I was getting too jealous.
I died a little on the inside.
Oh, I'm not saying that Iori-chan
was being mean or anything.
It hurt because she was right.
I was jealous of you because
you saved Yui and everyone
else while I did nothing.
I started avoiding you guys because
it was hard for me to swallow.
Honestly, I only saved them by chance.
Besides, it was for my own reasons
that I kept saying I
wanted to help Kiriyama.
Taichi, I'm sorry!
Aoki...
Can I come in?
Oh. No luck, huh?
She sent me packing before I
had a chance to talk to her.
But I'm going to drop
by her house again.
It's probably too soon for
us to tag along, right?
Do you think Iori-chan got
through to Inaba-chan this time?
She said she'll call if it goes well.
So since she hasn't called...
Taichi...
Let's sit down.
Doesn't it scream
adolescence when you see
two guys having a talk out here?
Let's enjoy our youth!
I don't think it's possible to do
something completely altruistic.
Yeah, in the end, everything
we do is for ourselves.
But I still...
Want to help Yui, right?
Yeah.
But I don't think we can do it ourselves.
Kiriyama has to let us help her.
Sure, but we have no idea how
long these episodes will continue,
and she can't hide in her room forever.
If Kiriyama has another episode,
we should be able to stop
her if we're there.
You think we can stop Yui?
If we're really careful
and try our best...
That's an old-fashioned
way of thinking.
I have no idea
how you were able to cure Yui's trauma.
I took your advice.
Huh?
You mentioned that
swapping personalities
presented us with new opportunities.
That's how I got the idea.
So maybe there's a solution
that's unique to
our current situation.
I-I think I have an idea.
Really?
Yui? Yui!
Your friends are here again.
Open the door, Yui!
Don't worry, "Mom"!
We'll talk to Yui-san!
Thank you for dropping by so often.
Please, I would do
anything for Yui-san!
Yui, it's me and Taichi.
We want to talk.
Can you open the door?
Come in.
It's been a while.
Uh-huh...
Yui, let's go outside.
Let's go to school.
You'll be fine.
How many times do I
have to repeat myself?
I don't know when I might
suddenly beat someone up.
I can't step outside.
But if you just hide in here forever,
this whole mess might never get fixed.
You'll be fine, Yui!
You can stop yourself
from beating someone up!
Don't be stupid!
I can try to stop myself,
but if I have an episode,
I'll lose control!
That's not true!
Even when your desire is unleashed,
if you try really, really hard
to stop yourself, it'll work!
It won't work when your
desire is unleashed.
You can't stop yourself.
That's how it works.
That's how it works, but
it's not how it works!
Huh?
I'm saying that you can stop yourself!
If I can prove that it's possible,
you'll be able to come outside,
come to school,
and come to the clubroom, right?
Well, if I can stop myself...
Okay, that's perfect!
I can't say I'm proud of it,
but I love you, Yui!
I really love you!
I love you so much! So, so much!
I'm also not proud to admit
that I have a dirty mind.
To be frank, my mind is
always in the gutter!
I'm thinking dirty thoughts!
Really dirty thoughts!
Wait, what are you talking about?!
And honestly, if I had
an episode right now,
I would be seconds away from
throwing myself on you!
Wh-What are you saying?!
That's despicable!
Wait! You've got it wrong!
Sicko!
I'm saying that my
ironclad determination will
stop me from doing that!
It proves that, if you're
determined enough,
you can fight back when your
desire is unleashed!
H-How stupid can you be?!
I have no idea what
you're trying to say!
Well, I guess I understand
what you mean.
Okay?
So, Yui...
Let's spend a night in a love hotel.
No way!
Why would I put myself in danger?!
Because nothing will happen.
How can you be so sure?!
Because the last thing I
want to do is hurt you.
Because I truly love you.
I'm confident that my
desire to not hurt you
will always be stronger.
Besides, on the off chance
that I do give in,
you would have no trouble
beating me to a pulp.
I don't want to hurt you.
In fact, you should wear
something sexy to tempt me.
Strip down to your underwear,
dress up like a bunny girl,
or wear nothing but an apron...
Stop fantasizing!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Come on, Taichi.
Seal the deal with
that gibberish of yours!
Don't call it gibberish before
I even say anything!
You guys are so stupid.
So let's hear your gibberish.
Don't join in, Kiriyama!
Anyway, I've been thinking.
Had you ever injured someone
or gotten violent before what
happened at the train station?
I practice karate, so
it's happened before.
But it didn't feel like I was
using violence to hurt someone
since it was during a match or practice.
That's what I thought.
That's why you didn't
understand what it
meant to hurt someone.
Right?
Uh-huh.
But now you understand how hard it is.
And you don't want to hurt anyone else.
Which means if you ever
want to beat someone up,
your desire to not hurt anyone
will probably triumph.
I guess you could consider not
wanting to do something a desire.
Actually, I hurt Nagase
the other day when I had an episode.
Huh?
So I think I kinda understand how you feel.
But I still want to be with you guys.
I'm guessing that you feel the same way.
You should believe in yourself more.
Good job, Taichi.
But you just made a
bunch of assumptions
with no concrete proof.
So let's go to a love hotel!
Stop talking about
going to a love hotel!
Mama's downstairs!
Kiriyama, your voice is too loud.
Oh, fine.
I'll go then.
What?!
No way!
To school!
But I'm still worried.
So...
If it looks like I'm losing control,
please stop me.
That's not the way to say it.
Huh?
Say this instead.
Please protect me?
It would be my honor!
Himeko?
Did your phone just ring?
Hey, are you okay?
You've been acting strangely again.
You're imagining things.
Yui!
W-Wait, Iori.
Yui?
You came to school, Yui!
That's great.
Sorry. Were you worried?
Of course we were. Silly girl.
We spent every day agonizing over
whether we should visit you or not.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, Kiriyama. You're back at school?
You look fine.
Yes, sorry about making everyone worry.
Did you put on some weight?
You're imagining things!
I think he's right.
Hey! Watch your mouth!
I hope Inaban also
comes to the clubroom.
So much!
Isn't this a little excessive?
I was only going to buy
enough for this week,
but I had an episode at the store.
I used up my allowance for the month.
It's too late to return them now.
Aoki?
Hey, Aoki?
Give me that mitarashi dango!
Desire unleashed?!
What?!
No way! Don't take mine!
Give me the mitarashi dango!
I wondered where this would lead...
There's more over there!
No! I absolutely must have yours!
Why do you want mine?!
That's mine!
Hold on, Nagase!
I already took a bite!
Grab another one!
I want the sandwich in your hand!
These are all mine!
You too, Kiriyama?!
Count me in!
Three at the same time?
Well, if it's just their hunger
that's being released,
that's not bad—
Eat!
Give me some!
Morning, Inaba.
Um, if you're worried about what you
said to me the other day,
I've gotten over it.
Come back to the clubroom.
We're all waiting for you.
Bye.
Himeko, you have a visitor.
It's Mr. Goto, your teacher.
Goto?
You're not here to tell me
that it's over, are you?
It's not over yet.
Were you surfing the web?
Why do you care?
Back in middle school,
that's all you ever did.
You spent all your time
outside class alone.
You couldn't trust anyone else.
You always put up barriers.
You were socially active enough that
you'd have no problems at school,
but you had no friends—
Enough!
I'm not interested in any of that.
If you need something, spit it out.
Have you forgotten, Inaba-san?
I told you that I would make
it entertaining if necessary.
Are you gonna toss me
in the river this time?
I thought that only applied
if we hid in our rooms.
Inaba-san, you're essentially
hiding in your room now.
That's not true. I'm going to school.
To prevent me from interfering?
You're a fascinating person, Inaba-san.
Can you get to the point?!
You didn't come here to make small talk.
Small talk...
That sounds about right.
I'm here to shake things up.
Shake things up?
Yes...
You're so uptight, Inaba-san.
Why are you so uptight?
Because you decided to mess
with us by unleashing our desires.
No, that's not what I mean.
Why do you care so
much about preserving
that atmosphere you
share with your friends?
If it's wearing you out,
you should tear it down.
Judging from your
current state of mind,
if your little group falls apart,
you'll try to destroy the world.
At least, that's what I was hoping.
Who are you?
Is the atmosphere you
shared what you care
about the most?
What?
Isn't there something else
you care about just as much?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, there most certainly is.
But you're trying desperately
to pretend you don't know.
Because you'll destroy your little group
if you let those feelings out.
Isn't there someone
you care for deeply?
Shut up!
You've become fully aware
of your own feelings.
There's no turning back now.
Once you know, it's
too late to run away.
Oh?
I didn't expect this to work so well.
I'm getting excited.
Can I sock you real hard?
I'll return control to this body's owner
the moment before you hit.
Are you going to visit anyone else?
You don't need to worry.
I made this trip just to see you.
Don't you find these
little twists entertaining?
Hell no.
And if you're able to
take control of anyone,
why did you use Goto instead
of a family member?
There are very few people who
wouldn't start asking questions when
they have blanks in their memory.
Stop trying to hide in your room.
Yo.
Inaba...
Morning!
We were wondering why you were late.
I wasn't gonna skip out
since I was responsible
for bringing the veggies.
Let's get going.
If we're late, Fujishima
will start griping.
It feels like it's been ages since
we just chatted about nothing.
Are the three of them doing okay?
That's the only way the five
of us can stay together!
What's that mean?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
She knows!
She knows! She knows!